question_data = [

    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The Xenomorph from the science fiction film Alien has acidic blood.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth "
                    "Vader.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, Alec Guinness provided the voice for Darth Vader.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "'Cube', 'Cube 2: Hypercube' and 'Cube Zero' were directed by the same person.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the movie The Revenant, DiCaprio's character hunts down the killer of his son.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "'Minions' was released on the June 10th, 2015.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "'Foodfight!' earned less than $80,000 at box office.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "YouTube personality Jenna Marbles served as an executive producer of the film Maximum Ride (2016).",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The original ending of 'Little Shop Of Horrors' has the plants taking over the world.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }

]
